

#### **EDUCATION**

Bachelor of Science in Computer Science Cavite State University - Silang Campus 2014 - 2018

# PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

Java
Javascript
AngularJS
ReactJS
NodeJS
Jest
MongoDB
SQL (MySQL)
Google Dialogflow
Amazon Lex

## CONTACT

P: +63 975 594 5594 E: saulmatthewreyes@gmail.com

# **ADDRESS**

011 Paredes st., San Vicente I, Silang, Cavite

# SAUL MATTHEW REYES

## **ABOUT**

A Software Developer with experience in providing technical assistance to clients and end-users, creating and improving SQL queries for precise data retrieval, developing web applications and utilizing AI technologies mainly Chatbots. Motivated to improve oneself and committed to deliver quality solutions.

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

#### **TECHNICAL SUPPORT ENGINEER**

Oracle NetSuite (Philippines) Corp. | 2022 - 2023

- Troubleshoot and provided technical assistance to client's issues and concerns via call and email.
- Documented detailed records of issues, resolutions, and client interactions

#### QUERY DEVELOPER

Jarvis Analytics Philippines OPC | 2021 - 2022

 Develop and modify SQL queries to retrieve and manipulate data from databases.

#### APPLICATION DEVELOPMENT ANALYST

Accenture Inc. | 2019 - 2021

- Developed and designed web applications based on client requirements.
- Experienced in both Front-end and Back-end side of web development
- Created and implemented unit testing for applications.
- Performed bug fixes for applications.
- Created functioning Chatbot conversation flows.
- Extensive experience working in an Agile development environment.
- Presented team updates and accomplishments during application release demos.
- Created documentations such as User Guides and Developer Setup.

# **CERTIFICATES**

AWS CLOUD PRACTITIONER
Apr 2021 - Apr 2024

OCI FOUNDATIONS 2021 ASSOCIATE
Feb 2022 - Feb 2024